<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on Created by Ira</title>
    <link>https://createdbyira.com/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on Created by Ira</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://createdbyira.com/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shoe Dog</title>
      <link>https://createdbyira.com/blog/shoe-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://createdbyira.com/blog/shoe-dog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day, Yura and I were walking through a mall, and I spotted an Onitsuka Tiger store. Just a few weeks ago, I would have walked right past it without a second thought. But now, I know exactly what that store represents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I just finished reading Shoe Dog—the memoir by the creator of Nike, Phil Knight. In it, he shares the story of how he built the company, the obstacles he faced, and how Nike barely kept its head above water for years—even while making millions. It’s a raw look at what he had to sacrifice to make the brand a success.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Built to Last</title>
      <link>https://createdbyira.com/blog/built-to-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://createdbyira.com/blog/built-to-last/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It took me several months to get through &lt;em&gt;Built to Last&lt;/em&gt;. There were pages I reread two or three times, moments where I’d put the book down for a day to let things sink in, and then return to them again. While many of the concepts weren’t entirely new to me, certain insights were genuinely surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, the book explores the principles that help build &amp;ldquo;visionary companies&amp;rdquo;—those that thrive for decades. Even if you don’t plan on launching a business, I highly recommend reading it. Many of these ideas apply to any project, including the most important one of all: life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
